Hello friends welcome to Five Minute Talk
youtube channel in this video we are going to
see about harassment of Money View.
Now you may have taken a loan from Money View. I have also taken a loan from
Money View.
Now I will show you how much I
have taken. I
open the Money View loan application. I have taken up
to 150000.
Before this, I have taken a
loan. I have completed it.
Now, is this loan the second time? I have taken this loan. I have taken a loan. I
click on it and see. Okay,
what are the EMI details?
We have enabled it.
Every month, I pay ₹7931.
Have you seen the EMI details? So, look here. I paid in the first month.
Now,
how many months are there? I paid
on time.
I paid for 12 months. A total of 24 months. Now,
only in the 13th month.  There is a little bit of a delay. There is a financial problem. The delay is a delay. If the delay is a delay,
we
will pay it. Okay, we are not going to leave it as it is. If we had to pay it, we could have left it unpaid from the first one. Okay, he has been paying it so
far. Now, he has
only paid this one. They have put an overcharge on it.
Look here. How much is the repayment delay?
17103. Actually, this one is the one that has to be paid.
Okay, that is,
pay it by January 5. Okay, look at the
repayment delay he has put on it.
Where is 7000? Where
is 17000? Where is ₹10000? Okay, he has
put an overdue payment and given a view break-up. He has put it
like he is paying two EMIs together.
Look at how big a big deal he is.
Then we have
to think about whether he should pay it or not.  Okay, we're going to go
home okay,
panel charge means penalty comes and
even if we put a ₹1000, we're going to go home okay,
he
came and sent a message on WhatsApp,
look, if you come and visit your wife and don't pay,
your EMI
will be changed to 24% from next month, how come the
interest rate will come and be charged anyway, no matter
how many times I called, I didn't
get the EMI, if I don't get the money today,
we will
reach your workplace or talk to your family
member, and so on, they called
two or three people saying, let them
call and
talk, look at what I sent, if it's changed to
24%, you won't
get any payment, I will
file a legal complaint, have you
seen that, then every time, I mean, I will
make this payment on the 26th, right, you're threatened like that  If you have
made a thread like this, don't
make any payment, that's my final decision, and we will
go further. We can complain to RBI. We will make a
lot of
complaints. Okay,
wherever we complain, we will
complain there. Because they say it's a
registered
app. They
say it's a registered app and they come and start behaving like this seven-
day application.
That's what I know. So don't be
afraid of these threads. Let's
see how many messages they have sent.
Look, in any case,
they won't come to us and not make the payment.
Okay, it's late,
but they charge a late charge. It doesn't
matter if the
payment comes and we make it. Okay, when we
make the correct payment,
one thing  He is doing two wrong things, right?
Because he doesn't just come and
give, that is, he has given a loan, then he comes and
collects it with interest.
Look at how much it is for 1000. We have to pay up to 3 lakhs,
that much double.
Then
he comes and collects our money. Right, when he comes and
collects like this, he shouldn't let
us come and collect.
Let's see.
This is one of the harassment. Right,
this money view, what else? I have bought many loan apps,
Hero Pin Corp. There are
some other loan apps. So, because there are
a lot of fake calls, they have
blocked all incoming calls, that is, they have
completely blocked incoming calls from unknown people. They say that even if you call, you cannot reach them. So,
what month is it pending?
Look, is it pending for four months now?
No, it is
pending for only one month, and that too for
this month.  It's appropriate that we come with this charge and
clear our land.
Have you seen their conversations during that? Okay, if you've received
harassment like this, then you
can try to be brave, boy.
I'll see you in the next video.